euroleague.net 2019-09-18

# EuroleagueID

## EUROLEAGUE BASKETBALL PRIVACY POLICY

Euroleague Ventures S.A. (also referred to as 'Euroleague Basketball', ‘Euroleague’, 'We', 'Our') provides you with the events official websites www.euroleague.net, www.eurocupbasketball.com, www.euroleaguebasketball.net, www.adidasngt.com, www.techchallenge.euroleague.net ('Euroleague Websites') and the Euroleague Basketball applications, including but not limited to mobile apps and tablet apps (together 'Euroleague Platforms'), including any services, sweepstakes, ticket purchase, raffles, contests, content and software ('Services'), subject to the following Privacy Policy ('Privacy Policy').

By using the Euroleague Platforms and/or Services, You or any person You allow to access and use Your account may provide Euroleague with or Euroleague collects certain personal data, including the Registration Data and certain other information about You. By accessing or using the Euroleague Platforms, or submitting Your personal information to the Euroleague Platforms, You agree to Euroleague’s use of such data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Euroleague Basketball takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy describing how we collect, handle and use personal information collected from users or visitors to the Euroleague Platforms and Services.

INFORMATION ABOUT US

We inform those who use the Euroleague Platforms and Services that all their personal data submitted to the Euroleague Basketball through the use of the Euroleague Platforms and Services will be stored in a database owned by Euroleague Ventures SA with address in 60, Grand-Rue, L-1660, Luxembourg. 

Our data protection officer can be contacted at data.protection.officer@euroleague.net

As the responsible for the processing of your data, Euroleague Basketball ensures that the processing of the personal data you provide takes place according to this privacy policy and in compliance with the provisions of current legislation on data protection and in the contest of the new regulatory framework established by virtue of the provisions of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council, of 27 April 2016, relating to the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and the free circulation of said data (the “GDPR”). 

We may communicate your personal data, to public organizations, judges and courts and, in general, competent authorities when we have the legal obligation to provide them and to some third-party services providers (which may be based outside the European Economic Area) as a consequence of the provision of services. Please note that we will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated as safely and securely as it would be within the European Economic Area and under the GDPR. Euroleague Basketball follows strict criteria of selection of service providers in order to comply with their obligations in terms of data protection and undertakes to sign with them the corresponding data processing contracts through which they will impose, among others, the following obligations: apply appropriate technical and organizational measures, use the personal data for the agrees purposes and attending only to the documented instructions of the Euroleague Basketball; and delete or return the data to Euroleague Basketball once the provision of services ends.

Euroleague Basketball has contracted the provision of services by a third-party provider in charge of data processing located in the United States, a country that does not belong to the European Economic Area. Euroleague Basketball has signed with this company a Type Contract Clauses that legitimize the international transfer of data.

SPECIFIC PURPOSES

Your data will be processed by Euroleague Basketball for the fulfillment of the following purposes:

Organization of services and events: draws, competitions and promotional events. In case you want to participate, you will sign up voluntarily by submitting the forms provided by Euroleague Basketball. 

Conducting market research and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients and send out e-mail alerts you may have signed up for.

Sending newsletters and magazines: information on the activities, events, services and products of the Euroleague Basketball and our sponsors and collaborators as long as you have consented to this service.

Conducting surveys: in order to verify the quality of communications, the services as well as the products we offer.

Information of promotions and commercial actions of our collaborators and sponsors: we will inform you of the development of any promotions and commercial actions conducted by our sponsors and collaborators by means of a general nature or adapted to your personal characteristics, as long as you have given your consent through the form established for that purpose. Also, we inform you that you can oppose and/or withdraw your consent for this service at any time.

Management of registration and cancelation of users: user registrations made through any Euroleague Platform, form or application. This information will allow us to know your profile and thus be able to make better offers and put at your disposal information that may be of interest to you about events and activities we organize. 

Management of the relationship with members (if applicable), including economic, accounting, fiscal and administrative management: management of your membership status, modification and/or updating of your data, modification of bank account details, monitoring of payments.

Processing of data relating to own and third-party cookies in order to analyze your browsing habits and improve services: you can consult the detail of the information on the cookies policy of Euroleague Basketball in the use of the aforementioned data in the following link. 

The legal basis for such processing will be the performance of the relationship between Euroleague Basketball and you, and for the cases expressly indicated above related to commercial communications, contests or promotional events, your express consent.

If you do not wish to receive marketing and promotional communications from us or our partners, sponsors, and affiliates, you can choose to opt-out when providing your Personal information to us or anytime by clicking the option “unsubscribe” available in all our press releases, advertising and newsletters.

 Please note: if you decide to opt-out of receiving information, we will be unable to keep you informed of any new products, services or special offers that may interest you and will have an impact on our ability to inform you of any events or important information as part of any subscription service you may have.

We will not transfer your personal data to any third parties except in those cases in which We might be legally obliged to do so or We receive any formal requirement form the Authorities.

INFORMATION COLLECTION 

Euroleague Basketball collects personal information when you visit or use the Euroleague Platforms or Euroleague products. Euroleague Basketball may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When using the Euroleague Platforms (and any related applications and services) or registering we may ask you to provide all or some of the following information: your name, e-mail address, gender, telephone number, country address, age and preferred basketball teams, amongst others (“Personal Information”). We may also ask you to provide your thoughts or answer some questions about your favorite events, team or sportsmen and other subjects of interest to basketball fans and information relevant to the commercial operations of the Euroleague Basketball. When you register to enjoy any of the Euroleague Basketball services and sign to use them, you are not anonymous to us.  

When you purchase any live events viewable on the Euroleague Platforms or participate in or access or sign up to any of the Euroleague Basketball services, activities or online content, such as newsletters or e-mail regarding upcoming events, competitions, web and mobile notifications, book tickets for an Euroleague Basketball event we may receive Personal Information about you as the services may not work properly without such information.

When we provide personalized services, we may ask your permission to review third party data about you, for example your Twitter, Instagram, Google+, VK, Facebook feeds, to get to know you better and to provide more effective personalization. Some of our services enable you to sign-in via a third –party service such as Facebook. If you choose to sign-in via a third-party app, you will be presented with a dialog box which will ask your permission to allow the Euroleague Basketball to access your Personal Information and any other information you have made publicly accessible. Please note that any information that is not required by the particular service you have opted to use will not be retained by the Euroleague Basketball. 

Likewise, Euroleague Basketball automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, Euroleague Basketball cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and your physical location and the page you request.

HOW LONG WILL WE KEEP YOUR DATA?

The personal information will be processed as long as they are accurate for the management of the purposes reported, and in particular until the relationship between Euroleague Basketball and you is in force Afterwards, Euroleague Basketball will keep the personal duly blocked during the period in which it might be legally required. 

Likewise,  and regarding commercial communications purposes, the information will be kept as long as you have not withdrawn your consent for this purposes. Euroleague Basketball will keep your data in order to keep you updated on Euroleague Basketball products, services and events that may be of interest to you. In case you withdraw your consent, Euroleague Basketball will keep the personal duly blocked during the period in which it might be legally required. 

WEB BROWSER COOKIES

Euroleague Basketball uses cookies in order to ensure the Euroleague Platforms function properly and to improve your user experience. Cookies are usually a string of numbers and/or letters that a website transfers to your hard drive. The cookies enable the website to remember you and to provide you with personalized visits to the Euroleague Platforms and the most user-friendly navigation experience, customize the advertising and content you see and recommend goods, services or promotions which may be of interest to you.

You may also set your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our services, or to indicate when a cookie is being set by us. However, it is important to remember that many of our services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

We recommend that you visit our Cookies Policy.

ADS DISPLAYED ON THIRD PARTY SITES

We may use third party advertising companies to serve ads. These companies may use information about your visits to the Euroleague Platforms and other websites in order to provide advertisements about events, goods and services of interest to you. 

WHAT IF I AM A USER AGED 14 OR UNDER?

Euroleague Basketball will not collect or process personal data for children under fourteen (14) years of age, without fully complying with the requirements established in the applicable data protection regulations, regarding compliance with the duty to inform and obtain those consents that they are necessary. 

YOUR RIGHTS UNDER CURRENT LAW

Under the GDPR you may exercise your right of access, rectification or deletion of data, request the processing to be restricted, oppose it or request data portability at any time by sending a written notice to Euroleague Ventures SA, 60 Grand-Rue L-1660 Luxembourg, or by sending an email to data.protection.officer@euroleague.net, clearly indicating the right you wish to exercise and attaching a copy of your national identification document or similar document proving your identity. You may also file a claim with the Agency for Data Protection.

QUESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS

If you have questions or suggestions concerning this Privacy Policy, including the treatment of your Personal Information and/or use of cookies and other technologies, you can contact us at: data.protection.officer@euroleague.net. We are happy to help and we will do our best to respond in a timely manner.
